

Visual User Interface Designer

I love designing beautiful products. My 12 years of digital design experience allowed me to shape a part of the internet to be easier to use, accessible and responsive, while supporting stakeholders and engineers through development.

I've always been obsessed with the power of a great visual experience. The last 6 years of only working on products, I've specialized in solving complex visual problems for large applications and holding them to the highest design standards.

pdr.laguna@gmail.com

+55 53 9 9179 0260

https://pedrolaguna.com.br

Education

Instituto Federal Sul-Riograndense BA in Design

2012 - 2016 (Dropped Out)

Founded a club that later became the seed to a design school like Coletivo HOW.

Instituto Federal Sul-Riograndense

Technical in Visual Communication

2009 - 2011 (Dropped Out)

Experience

Checkplant · Product Designer

2016 - Present

I lead the design team at Farmbox while we shape the future of agriculture in Brazil. From creating an entire design system to building products that help thousands of farmers' work daily.

Freelancer · Visual Designer

2007 - 2016

I always loved working with tight constraints. For that, local businesses were great. But there's a limit to what design alone could do to impact a business. Developing product design skills and delivering it with great visual design was game changer for me (and my clients too).

AG2 Nurun • UX Designer

2014 - 2015

We were on a mission to change the UI of banks with Banco Bradesco and that team set in motion the shift in mentality we see on the bank today. Researching and designing core banking experiences (like a whole ATM!) was influential in my approach to designing systems.

Izyplay Game Studio • UI/UX Designer

2012 - 2014

As the first hired I had to wear a lot of different hats. Delivering high-level mockups, prototypes, and wireframes, but also taking care of the UI and the look and feel of all projects. It was crazy and amazing! Many games and apps helped shape brands like Sprite and Webmotors.

AG2 Publicis Modem • Information Architect

2009 - 2011

It was before "UX" was even a thing. I've helped the social media team with information architecture and visual design of custom made dashboards and reports. A lot of craft and time was put into delivering results for product launches of brands likes Chevrolet, Embraer, Natura, and others.